Local 1199 Drug Division Records 5206-D
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Drug Division Records
1929-1973
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU)
RWDSU Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union
5206-D
72 cubic feet
72 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Records of the National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees document the evolution of the Retail, Wholesale and Department Store drugstore local, representing pharmacists and drug clerks in New York City, into an international union of non-professional and professional workers in voluntary and non-profit health institutions, including hospitals, clinics and nursing homes, as well as drugstores.
6694245
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Connie Bulkley, August 29, 2003
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Biographical / Historical
Between 1933 and 1957, 1199 functioned as a drugstore local with its membership growing to 5,000 workers employed in independent and chain drugstores throughout the New York metropolitan area. With its success in organizing workers in Montefiore Hospital in New York City, the union began a massive campaign to organize workers in voluntary and non-profit hospitals in the New York area, a large proportion of whom were black or Hispanic.
In 1973, the national union was established with locals in other states, including Pennsylvania, Maryland, South and North Carolina, Connecticut, New Jersey, and Massachusetts. The union combined organizing efforts with civil rights organizations, in an effort to achieve mutual political goals. Throughout the period of these records, the union was led by Leon Davis (president of Local 1199 and of the national union) whose administration guided the union's political and social activities.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5206: Local 1199 Records 5206-G: Local 1199 Guild Division Records 5206-PR: Local 1199 President Leon Davis Records 5206-S: Local 1199 Executive Secretary Moe Foner Records 5206-X: Local 1199 Clippings and News Releases 5457: Mark Lillian Collection of Roosevelt Hospital (NYC) vs. Local 1199, 1962 Representational Dispute Documents 5510: Local 1199 Records 5520m: "Building a Union in the Hospitals: the Organization of Local 1199 at Montefoire Hospital, 1948-1958" Manuscript 5525: Local 1199 Additional Files 5651: Local 1199 Additional Records 5768: Sidney Cahn Collection of League of Voluntary Hospitals & Homes of New York vs. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union Arbitration Files 5680 OH: Local 1199 Oral History Project 5854: Local 1199 Additional Records 5871: Local 1199 Additional Records 5929: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Records 5929 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 5929 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 5929 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 5933: Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union News files 5933 P: Local 1199 Photograph Files 5938: Local 1199 Leon Davis Additional Papers 5945: Local 1199 Additional Records 5948: Local 1199 (Rochester, N.Y.) Records 5984 AV: Local 1199 Additional Videos 5984 AV: Local 1199 Additional Videos 6016: Local 1199 National Benefit and Pension Fund Records 6062: Paul Friedman Collection of National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199 Miscellany 6069: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Additional Files 6084 G: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Women of Hope Poster Sets 6140: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project 6140 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio Recordings 6140 P: Local 1199 Moe Foner Photographs 6169: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Files 6169 AV: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Audio-Visual Materials 6169 MB: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Memorabilia 6169 P: Local 1199 Bread and Roses Cultural Project Photographs 6209 AV: 1199SEIU Audio-Visual Materials 6209 PUBS: Local 1199 Publications 6281m: Local 1199 Biography files 6347: 1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Records 6347 PUBS: 1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Publications
Health facilities -- Labor unions -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Health facilities -- United States; Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union; National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees. District 1199; Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union (New York, N.Y.)
6694245
- Old boxes 1, 1a, 2 (Box 1)
  - Constitutions, 1938-1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitutions, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Constitutions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Constitutions, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Constitutions, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Constitutions, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Constitutions, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constitutions, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Constitutions, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Constitutions, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Constitutions, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Constitutions, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Constitutions, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Constitutions, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Constitutions, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Constitutions, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Constitution, 1938-1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Scope and Contents
    Workcopies and Amendments
  - Constitution, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Constitution, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Constitution, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Constitution (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Minutes, 1933-1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Minutes, 1933-1940 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Minutes, 1933-1940 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Minutes (Feb.-Mar.), 1940 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Minutes, 1940-1943 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Old boxes 3-6, 6a (Box 3)
  - Minutes, 1943-1947 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1943-1947 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, August, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1947-1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1947-1953 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1947-1953 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Old boxes 7-9 (Box 7)
  - Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Old boxes 10-13 (Box 10)
  - Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Appeals, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Appeals, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Charges, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Charges, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Charges, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Charges, 1957-1961 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Charges, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Charges, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Reports, 1949-1952 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Old boxes 14-16 (Box 14)
  - Minutes, 1937-1939 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1939-1947 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1947-1949 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1947-1949 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1950-1956 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1957-1960 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Reports, 1947-1949 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Reports, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Old boxes 17-19 (Box 17)
  - Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1951-1957 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1951-1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1951-1957 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Old boxes 20-22 (Box 20)
  - Minutes, 1958-1962 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1958-1962 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1958-1962 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Bronx, 1951-1961 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn, 1951-1961 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn, 1951-1961 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn, 1951-1961 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn, 1951-1961 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Long Island, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Lower Manhattan, 1951-1961 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lower Manhattan, 1951-1961 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lower Manhattan, 1951-1961 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Lower Manhattan, 1951-1961 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Midtown, 1951-1962 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Midtown, 1951-1962 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Midtown, 1951-1962 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Queens, 1951-1962 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Queens, 1951-1962 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Queens, 1951-1962 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Old boxes 23-25 (Box 23)
  - Upper Manhattan, 1951-1959 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Upper Manhattan, 1951-1959 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Upper Manhattan, 1951-1959 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Upper Manhattan, 1951-1959 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Upper Manhattan, 1951-1959 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - West Midtown, 1953-1954 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Drops and Withdrawals, 1956-1958 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Excuses (Delegates), 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Excuses (Delegates), 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Area Reports (Monthly Shop Meetings), 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Area Reports (Delegate Assembly), 1964-1967 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Reports-Bronx, 1957-1961 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Reports-Bronx, 1957-1961 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Reports-Brooklyn, 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Reports-Brooklyn, 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Reports-Brooklyn, 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Reports-Long Island, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Reports-Lower Manhattan, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Reports-Midtown, 1951-1955 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Reports-Queens, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Reports-Upper Manhattan, 1953-1957 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Reports-Uptown, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Old boxes 26-28 (Box 26)
  - Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1945-1947 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    1945 (May); 1947 (Dec.)
  - Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1945-1947 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Reports, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Reports, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Reports, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Reports, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Reports, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Reports, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Reports, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Reports, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Reports, 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Reports, 1946-1955 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Old boxes 29-31 (Box 29)
  - Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1949-1962 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Benefit Fund Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Old boxes 32-34 (Box 32)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Pension Fund Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Minutes, 1938-1941 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Minutes, 1938-1941 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Old boxes 35-37 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Minutes, 1951-1956 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Minutes, 1956-1962 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Minutes (Liggett), 1949 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Minutes (Liggett & Whelan), 1950-1959 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Pharmacy-Classes, lectures, 1957-1962 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Pharmacy-General, 1954-1969 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Pharmacy-General, 1954-1969 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Pharmacy-General, 1954-1969 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Pharmacy-In Industry, 1956-1958 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Pharmacy-Italian Pharmacists, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Pharmacy-Medication Costs, 1959-1960 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Pharmacy-Publications, Press, etc., 1957-1961 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Old boxes 38-40 (Box 38)
  - Pharmacy-Committee (Emergency) for Pharmacy and Public Health, 1960-1961 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Pharmacy-Committee (Special) on Sub-Professionals, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Pharmacy-Drug Plans, 1959-1961 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Pharmacy-Drum Cooke Bill, 1954-1959 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Pharmacy-Industry Advisory Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Pharmacy-Legislation, 1958-1962 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Pharmacy-Training, 1963-1965 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Pharmacy-Training, 1963-1965 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Pharmacy-Training, 1963-1965 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Pharmacy-Training, 1963-1965 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Pharmacists-Appeals, 1960-1963 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Pharmacists-Career & Salary Board, 1956-1960 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Pharmacists-Hospital, 1956-1966 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Pharmacists-Organization, 1957-1960 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Pharmacists-Protest Letters, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Old boxes 41-43 (Box 41)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1965 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1965 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1965 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1965 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1965 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1965 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1965 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - NYS Pharmaceutical Society, 1944-1961 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - NYS Pharmaceutical Society, 1944-1961 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Security Fund Trustees, Minutes, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Security Fund, Correspondence & Reports, 1947-1954 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Strike Committee, Minutes, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Strike Committee, Minutes, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Welfare Committee, Minutes, 1946-1949 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Welfare Plan, Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Minutes, 1940-1952 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Old boxes 44-46 (Box 44)
  - Reports on Activities of the Union, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Reports on Activities of the Union, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Reports on Activities of the Union, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Reports on Activities of the Union, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Reports on Activities of the Union, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Reports on Activities of the Union, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Activities Reports, 1964-1970 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Benefit and Pension Reports, 1961-1967 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Elections, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Reports of the Employment Department, 1950-1955 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Employment- Monthly Job Reports, 1950-1959 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Employment- Monthly Job Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Insurance, 1945-1951 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Yearly Membership Inventories, 1945-1959 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Yearly Membership Inventories, 1960-1963 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Yearly Membership Inventories, 1953-1963 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Reports-Stewarts, 1961-1963 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Statistical Reports, 1959-1967 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - American Pharmaceutical Association, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Drug Division-General, 1968-1971 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Drug Division-N.Y.C. Advisory Committee on Pharmacy, 1966-1967 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Drug Forms, 1964-1965 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Pharmacists, 1968-1970 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Glotzer, George-Correspondence, 1958-1971 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Glotzer, George-Correspondence, 1958-1971 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Glotzer, George-Correspondence, 1958-1971 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Old boxes 47-49 (Box 47)
  - Independent Stores-Grievances, 1965-1969 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Independent Stores-Grievances, 1965-1969 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Jobs (Job Opportunities in Drug Stores), 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Mayor's Commission on Inflation & Economic Welfare, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - McCarthy Rally, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Medicaid Boycott, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Membership-General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Memos, Directives, etc., 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1963-1970 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Northeastern University Pharmacy Students, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Organization-Out of Town, 1966-1970 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Organization-Out of Town, 1966-1970 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Organization-Out of Town, 1966-1970 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Publications, 1963-1970 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - State Civil Service Pharmacists-Organization, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Yagoloff, Philip-Pathmark, 1968-1970 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence-Affiliations, 1952-1959 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence-Associations, 1951-1952 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence-Fraternal Organizations, 1950-1951 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence G-H, 1939-1940 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence-General, 1950-1963 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence-General, 1950-1963 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence-General, 1950-1963 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence-Glotzer, 1959-1962 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Old boxes 50-52 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence-Membership, 1956-1963 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence-NYS Dept. of Labor, 1946-1950 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-Organizations, 1957-1961 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence-T, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence-Thanks Letters, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence-Unions, 1948-1963 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence-Unions, 1948-1963 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence-Unions, 1948-1963 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence-Bronx, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence-Bronx, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence-Bronx, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence-Bronx, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence-Bronx, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence-Brooklyn, 1952-1966 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence-Brooklyn, 1952-1966 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence-Brooklyn, 1952-1966 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence-Brooklyn, 1952-1966 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence-Brooklyn, 1952-1966 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence-Central Manhattan, 1964-1966 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence-Lower Manhattan, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence-Lower Manhattan, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence-Midtown, 1952-1961 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence-Midtown, 1952-1961 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence-Midtown, 1952-1961 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence-Midtown, 1952-1961 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence-Queens, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence-Queens, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence-Queens, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence-Queens, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence-Queens, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence-Queens, 1952-1965 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence-Upper Manhattan, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence-Upper Manhattan, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence-Upper Manhattan, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 34)
- Old boxes 53-55 (Box 53)
  - AFL-CIO National, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - ACLU, 1954-1955 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Appeals-Classification, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 12)